since now Lamplight and MS Word, that is,
small and medium businesses are the backbone of the Indian economy.
A big part of this segment is the detail merchant.
ICICI Bank, the second largest private sector bank in the country, has
launched digital banking for them. We are here to
talk to you about merchants in this regard. ICICI
Bank shares subscribe to A.
Pappu ji, you are welcome and I would like to wish
you all the best for starting this. First of all,
tell us about the merchant platform. In the situation of Corona virus,
how will the merchants benefit from this?
Today I would like to remind you that last
year such a bank had launched some kind of platform, in which
two-three things
were in that package. Meena, first of all, all the
banking services
were digital in it, Meena, and it had a lot of facilities
for the customers and the most important
thing was that the customer could
experience these services sitting at his home.
Under this,
you have named a segment which  That the
merchants are grocery shops,
for them we have
launched a plugin by writing the text Super Mario Ask, in which all the same
principles are there because now as
I said, digital and all the
facilities of banking and payment are
dependent on one place and all these
services depend on one place, so the most important
issue is that during this
time of crisis, we are going through a
very difficult phase, at that
time our customers and our customers,
grocery shops and our merchants have
a big responsibility,
thankfully, all these services are
contactless, that is, contactless and that is why
we have taken all the services of this payment bank at one place,
I am saying this because there are
merchants who will get all kinds of services from customers,
merchants tag
is basically based on five major pillars,
we want to know from you in detail about these pillars,
first of all tell us about the system of this track, if it is a
banking service then the first base pillar is
that we have  A new account has been launched in which the
balance has to be kept at zero. If the customer has
no comment on the balance, then the biggest thing is that
its second important thing is that
the first term is that
your account can be
opened instantly and easily. This means that
you will have to meet our employees before the account is created,
but before that, all the processes can be
deleted. The third important
thing is that when a merchant has to
collect money from a different customer, there are
200 meters of different types of phones
which are available in Clark and in that,
cost machines are available. The
first type of different types of phones are available.
You can also use payment. So these are four-
five ways through which they can
collect money from their customers. The
last and important feature
of our first philosophy is that we
started a service called credit banking.
After last year, it has become clear that
whichever merchant adopts this service, they
use the meeting software or billing
software.  So
they can connect with our banking service and it will happen
that for those who are very busy, their
time spent in dealing with the
development bank will be reduced completely.
So all these facilities are based on our first plan. The
facilities being provided by Merchants Packs are very attractive
and special in their own way. Tell us about these facilities in detail,
how will this benefit the merchants and what
parameters will be used by the bank to share the customer's
actions. So the most
important question is getting the payment on time.
This is a very important facility for
our Redemption customers and to make them
aware of this, we have launched a very simple
Fit 2 Progress, which is
completely digital and
you can get the great facility that you need. You have
not read its first problem, its
name is merchants having to create a savings mode.
Like normally, when someone places an order,
merchants have to send their bank statement and
their income tax return through the operation,
which is time consuming and also takes time.
Look at how we have done it.  The
merchant who is always doing
transactions is in the business for so many years
and there are many other parameters
that we have used them and
filled it on the basis of which we are giving a merchant the best
mode of activity up
to ₹2500000 and this service is
also for those customers who are new, this breakfast is available
for them also if their
other parameters are in accordance with our score card
then we can offer them and
along with that facility our
customer can exchange the currency in minutes, the second
service is very interesting that is
when a customer
goes to the machine or does the
function on Monday after cutting his stomach,
firstly his settlement is done through the network
itself and if he has done it for Saturday-Sunday
then he gets tips, keeping this issue
in mind the service we have created is
called Express Print where
we have done cheese congestion with its network
provider and we have made a line  We have created an
app that helps us with
retail customer transactions
and keeping the registry
merchant in mind. We have
created an express message where the merchant receives the
settlement immediately.
If he takes the express
rate from the bank for the normal settlement,
he will receive this statement immediately. We have provided some of the time required for
his working capital graph
in our facilities, which
we have provided as a friend in this program.
We want to help the merchant convert his grocery
shop into an online shop.
What will be the process
and how much time will it take?
Tell us something about it. We meet a lot of people.
Many of our customers understand that
they interact, so it has become very
important that the merchant has the
power and it is said that he needs a medium through which he can
easily
reach the customer and such a medium was also needed.  If
your distributor is suffering from nightmares, then
through our Tukur Mazak,
we have introduced a service
called Digital Store Management.
When a merchant downloads our install this application, the
service Editor
for Management in it gets such fame
and remember that his shop which is a
physical store today gets converted into an online store, that is, through an
online store, he can easily forget
his troubles through a text message, this link
and the customers do not.
But suppose the
physical shop shown by the customer will appear as an
online shop in his Airtel customer care mobile
and the customer will place his order, whether it is
his motor, grocery items or any other
item, from his mobile or his
laptop, this will do two things.
Firstly, it saves time for the merchant.
Secondly, in today's era, when
customers are not coming to the store, online
service is available, it is
contactless, it is completely spontaneous
and this makes it possible to
use it on Willing To Alert.  It has to be done and
apart from the payment, both have one
hand and one service in it and apart from this, in all the
catalogs that we go, the
thing which is used the most in
our house, generally this Jyoti, all those cut
blouses are big scientists, we have
loaded it only in the proper, due to which
if that Kiran Akash you are or on the other hand
if you should also do quarter then
see its turnoff, you can also use your order for its
supply, this answer is this way when
you download the relation,
this service becomes available to him within 30 minutes to 1 hour, in
this special situation, the other two Khan
Sitam which you would like to be informed, then I
swear what I will say is that we have launched
quality products, so we have launched
this report, similarly
for the class questions of these customers, we have
launched a loyalty program, as the
business grows, we will add it, so that
urik which is
not in the market for the first time
someone has danced and
we have provided value added services to the fifth yellow
and  Let's go to the thing inside the table, the first thing
is that we have a very famous mobile
application, for this we can
understand it like this, its name is Inch Coffin Hudgens,
you can see more than 10 lakh activities in it, it
means
more than 10 lakh services are available to it, so if
we have embedded it in the above mentioned way in that mobile application itself, then
all the services will be available to
our customers, secondly
we have done the judgment services,
our merchant customers have some other
requirements too, like there is
safety requirement, there is computer
literacy requirement, so for that
we have made alliances, so as it is going to be, the
merchant can facilitate and have
all these services and the company has them
and the third point which is inside it and what happens with it is that
when our customer does
prayer in the morning, then he gets access
to our cooperative bank platform
and if any merchant
wants to import or export, then for that
we have built the test online feature,
whatever service he gets if  If I talk about
anti-venom and
briefly explain the five pillars, then the most
important thing is that the shopkeeper has to
spend his time in his business,
not in banking, and do not
ignore this thing, do you keep this
in mind, do you not notice that, but keeping this in
mind, we have
blocked the Manjan road in the morning so that he can spend his
time in the right place and more fancy is a
big sin
and Pankaj ji, thank you with all respect for your
entire conversation with us, I know that those people
who want to know about it in detail must have got all the solutions,
thank you,
in this changing world, these things are changing
online, we have made these things easy
and the business will
get good exposure through profitable online shop and the earnings will also be
good, I hope you
liked our conversation, if you still have some time
left, then definitely visit the bank's website,
all your doubts will be cleared.